<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sydney Open Research Network</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sydney Open Research Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CAPOS</title>
      <link>/community/capos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/community/capos/</guid>
      <description>Canadian-Australian Partnership for Open Scholarship The Canadian-Australian Partnership for Open Scholarship (CAPOS) is a collaboration between Canadian and Australian researchers, policy makers, libraries, computing organizations, research groups, and postsecondary institutions to advance the understanding of, and resolve crucial issues in, the production, distribution, and engagement of open, digital scholarship. CAPOS comprises the INKE Partnership and Australian-based partners.
This partnership capitalizes on both countries’ positive track records of participating in, engaging, and influencing the international consideration of open, digital scholarship issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DH Downunder</title>
      <link>/community/dhdownunder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/community/dhdownunder/</guid>
      <description>DH Downunder DH Downunder is a Digital Humanities / Digital Research Methods Summer Institute in the tradition of DHSI and similar international summer institutes. We provide training in cutting edge Digital Research methods and approaches. People with all kinds of backgrounds are welcome, including students, academic staff, PhD and postdoctoral researchers, librarians and professional staff. The classes have a humanities/social sciences orientation, but we are also very happy to have participants from other disciplinary backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Vision for the Open Research Network</title>
      <link>/post/a-vision-for-the-open-research-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/a-vision-for-the-open-research-network/</guid>
      <description>What are the goals of the Open Research Network? As per the about section, the open research network exists to support the adoption of open research practices. What differs from other approaches is that this is deliberately and explicitly about putting people in contact in the real world, to reduce the barriers to entry, and minimise the risk of alienation that arises from context collapse on social media.
To that end, it aims to support the proliferation of institutional open science communities, like the successful model of the Open Science Community Utrecht, to provide a welcoming, non-judgemental learning environment at a local level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sydney Coding Club</title>
      <link>/community/codingclub/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 16:54:54 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/community/codingclub/</guid>
      <description>Sydney Coding Club The coding club was motivated by ozunconf 2018. The plan is to adopt a similar format to ozunconf and let the participants drive the agenda. You come to the designated place and work as much or as little on coding project you want. The idea is to be surrounded by people who wants to code! People are free to sit down and work on their own or work with others on a project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sydney Research Bazaar</title>
      <link>/community/resbaz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 16:54:54 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/community/resbaz/</guid>
      <description>ResBaz: Research Bazaar The Research Bazaar is a free, 3-day intensive festival and conference where researchers come together to up-skill in next generation digital research tools and scholarship. In the spirit of a marketplace or bazaar, ResBaz is a highly participatory event where researchers from many different disciplines can learn, share knowledge and skills, and have fun. Throughout 2018 ResBaz events will be held at a number of university campuses around the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>